A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Education, 2006-2014 (bulk 2009-2013)
Library of Virginia
- II. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Department of Criminal Justice Service (DCJS) 2012 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles (DMV) 2013 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Domestic Violence Prevention 2011 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Early Childhood 2011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Early Childhood 2012 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Early Childhood Advisory Council (ECAC) 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Early Childhood Advisory Council (ECAC) 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (1 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (2 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (3 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (4 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (5 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Early Childhood Foundation 2010-2011 (6 of 6) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Early Childhood Innovation 2012 (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Early Childhood Innovation 2012 (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Early Childhood Innovation 2012 (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Early Childhood Readiness 2012 (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Early Childhood Readiness 2012 (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Early Childhood Readiness 2012 (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Early Intervention 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Economic Trends 2012 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Education Reform Summit 2012 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Electronic Textbooks 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - eMedia VA 2012 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Families for Honor 2010-2013 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Farm to School Task Force 2007 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fellows 2010-2013 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - First Cities 2012 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Fishburne Military Junior College 2011 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Future Leaders in Project Management (FLIPM) 2012 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - George Washington University 2011 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - George Mason University (GMU) Immunology Center 2011 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - George Mason University (GMU) Korea Campus 2012 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Governor's Cabinet Exercise 2010 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Governor's Education Symposium 2012 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Governor's K-12 Education Reform Summit 2013 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Governor's Forum 2011 2011 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gunston Hall 2012 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gunston Hall 2012 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Health Reform 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education Advisory Committee 2013 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education Efficiency and Productivity 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education Efficiency and Productivity 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Higher Education Commission(s) 2010-2011 (1 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education Commission(s) 2010-2011 (2 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education Commission(s) 2010-2011 (3 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education Commission(s) 2010-2011 (4 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - House Appropriations Committee 2013 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Igbo Farm Village 2010 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Inauguration 2010 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Instruction Briefings 2011 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - IT Academies/Training 2011-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - IT Academies/Training 2011-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2013 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson Lab - Southeastern Universities Research Association (SURA) 2011 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jobs for Virginia 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Juvenile Detention Education 2011 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Juvenile Re-Entry 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Juvenile Re-Entry 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - K-12 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Kindergarten Readiness 2012 (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kindergarten Readiness 2012 (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kindergarten Readiness 2012 (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kinship 2012 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Liberty University Report 2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Literacy 2011 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Loudoun Math and IT Academy 2011 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Maggie L. Walker Governor's School 2011 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Military Children and Families 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - MODSIM 2011 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Museum Directors 2010-2013 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - National Academy of Environmental Design (NAED Ni Village) 2010-2012 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - National Governor's Association (NGA) 2010 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - National Governor's Association (NGA) 2010-2012 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - National Governor's Association (NGA) 2010-2012 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - National Governor's Association (NGA) 2012 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - New College Institute 2010 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New School Venture Summit 2011 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Institute of Standards and Technology - University of Virginia (NIST - UVA) 2010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Northern Virginia Literacy 2012 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Norfolk State University 2011 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Norfolk State University Audit 2011-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk State University Audit 2011-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - University of Mary Washington - Dahlgren 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2011 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Old Dominion University - Virginia Mathematics and Science Coalition (ODU - VAMSC) 2011 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Patrick Henry Charter School 2011 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - P20 Readiness 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Preschool 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Preschool 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Preschool 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Project Rebuild 2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Promise - East End Achievement Zone 2011 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Project Discovery 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Radford University 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Re-Entry Commission on Youth 2010 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Re-Entry Council 2011 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Re-Entry Council 2011 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Re-Entry Council 2011 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Re-Entry Executive Summary 2010-2014 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Re-Entry: Housing 2010-2011 (1 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Re-Entry: Housing 2010-2011 (2 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Re-Entry: Housing 2010-2011 (3 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Re-Entry: Housing 2010-2011 (4 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Re-Entry: One Stop Behind the Walls 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Re-Entry: One Stop Behind the Walls 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Re-Entry: One Stop Behind the Walls 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Re-Entry Programs 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Re-Entry Programs 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Research and Technology Initiatives 2010-2012 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Research and Technology Initiatives 2010-2012 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Research and Technology Initiatives 2010-2012 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Regional Strategies 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Race to the Top Early Learning Challenge (RTT ELC) 2013 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Rules Program 2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (1 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (2 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (3 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (4 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (5 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (6 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (7 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (8 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - School and Campus Safety Task force 2012-2013 (9 of 9) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schools Not Fully Accredited 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): 2013 Agenda 2013 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Assessment Report 2012 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): College Access Report 2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Eminent Scholars 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Financial Aid 2010-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Financial Aid 2010-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Presentations 2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV): Valley Forge 2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Social Impact Bond 2011 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Soundscapes 2011 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Southern Virginia Higher Education Center 2010 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Southside Virginia Community College 2012 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Southside Virginia Community College 2012 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) 2010-2012 (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) 2010-2012 (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) 2010-2012 (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) 2010 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) Tract 2012 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Science, Technology, Engineering and Math(STEM) Tract 2012 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Strategic Plan for Education 2010-2013 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Tax Credit 2013 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Teacher Cabinet 2013 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Transition Committee 2010 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Transition Committee - Assessment 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Transition Committee - Board of Education 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Transition Committee - Appendix 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Transition Committee - Appendix 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Transition Committee - Appendix 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Transition Committee - Christopher Newport University 2009-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Transition Committee - Commission for the Arts 2010 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Catholic Conference 2010 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Catholic Conference 2010 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Transition Committee - Council on Economic Education 2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Transition Committee - Diocese of Richmond 2010 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Transition Committee - Department of Education 2010 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Transition Committee - Finance 2010 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Transition Committee - Frontier Culture Museum 2010 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Transition Committee - Great Aspirations Scholarship Program (GRASP) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Transition Committee - George Mason University (GMU) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Transition Committee - Gunston Hall 2010 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Transition Committee - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2010 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Transition Committee - Instructional 2010 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Transition Committee - James Madison University (JMU) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Transition Committee - Library of Virginia (LVA) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Transition Committee - Longwood University 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Transition Committee - Longwood University 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Transition Committee - University of Mary Washington 2010 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Transition Committee - Norfok State University (NSU) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Transition Committee - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Transition Committee - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Transition Committee - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Transition Committee - Radford University 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Transition Committee - Radford University 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Transition Committee - Radford University 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Transition Committee - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Transition Committee - Science Museum 2010 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Transition Committee - Standards of Quality (SOQ) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Transition Committee - Special Education 2010 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Transition Committee - Teacher Education 2010 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Transition Committee - Technology 2010 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Transition Committee - University of Virginia (UVA) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Transition Committee - University of Virginia (UVA) - Wise 2010 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Commonwealth University(VCU) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts(VMFA) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia Military Institue(VMI) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia School for the Death and Blind (VSDB) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Transition Committee - Virginia State University(VSU) 2010 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Troops to Teachers 2010 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - University of Phoenix 2012 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - University of Virginia (UVA) - Wise 2011 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Virginia Adopts 2010-2013 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Virginia Latino Higher Education Network (VALHEN) 2013 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Policy Venture - New Orleans 2012 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Virginia Tech 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) 2009-2011 (1 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) 2009-2011 (2 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) 2009-2011 (3 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) 2009-2011 (4 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) - Analysis 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) - Analysis 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Virginia Community College System(VCCS) 2010-2013 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Virginia Community College System(VCCS) HIRE Conference Keynote 2011 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Virginia Community College System(VCCS) State Board Meeting 2009-2010 (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Virginia Community College System(VCCS) State Board Meeting 2009-2010 (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Virginia Community College System(VCCS) - Workforce 2010 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Virginia Private Colleges 2013 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Initiative for Education and Workforce Development (VIEW) 2013 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Virtual Schools 2010-2011 (1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Virtual Schools 2010-2011 (2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Virtual Schools 2010-2011 (3 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Virtual Schools 2010-2011 (4 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Virtual Schools 2010-2011 (5 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Virtual Library of Virginia (VIVA) 2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - William and Mary 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Workforce Council 2010 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Workforce Council 2011 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Workforce Council 2012 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- III. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  This series includes both constituent correspondence and official correspondence amongst cabinet members and other officials. This series arrived with a general order that distinguished between K-12, and Higher Education related correspondence from General correspondence and Gold Sheets. This grouping was respected by the processing archivist. Some of the notable topics found in the correspondence include For more correspondence, also see Series V: Decision Briefs and Supporting Documentation.
  - K-12: Bullying 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - K-12: Charter Schools/Home Schools 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - K-12: Class Size 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - K-12: Curriculum 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - K-12: Exercise/Food 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - K-12: Funding/Teacher Pay 2010-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - K-12: Funding/Teacher Pay 2010-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - K-12: Lottery 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - K-12: Preschool 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - K-12: Project Discovery 2013 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - K-12: Quality of Education 2012 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - K-12: Reading 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - K-12: Special Needs 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - K-12: Specific Schools 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - K-12: Specific Schools 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - K-12: Standards of Learning (SOL) 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - K-12: Qualified Bonds 2011 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - K-12: General Correspondence 2010-2013 (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - K-12: General Correspondence 2010-2013 (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - K-12: General Correspondence 2010-2013 (3 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - K-12: Common Core State Standards (CCSS) 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Higher Education: Financial Aid 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Higher Education: Financial Aid 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Higher Education: General Correspondence 2010-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Higher Education: General Correspondence 2010-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Higher Education: Memoranda of Understanding (MOUs) 2011 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Higher Education: Memoranda of Understanding (MOUs) 2012 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Higher Education: Memoranda of Understanding (MOUs) 2013 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2011 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2012 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Higher Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Higher Education: Specific 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Higher Education: Tuition Assistance Grant (TAG) 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Higher Education: William and Mary 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Higher Education: Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2010-2013 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Higher Education: University of Virginia (UVA) 2011 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Higher Education: Virginia Commonwealth University(VCU) 2011-2013 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Higher Education: Virginia Tech 2011-2013 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Higher Education: Virginia Community College System (VCCS) 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Gold Sheets 2012-2013 (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Gold Sheets 2012-2013 (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Gold Sheets 2012-2013 (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence 2010 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence 2010 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence 2011 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence 2011 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (1 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (2 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (3 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence 2011 2011 (4 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (1 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (2 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (3 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (4 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence 2012 2012 (5 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence - Department of Education 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence - Gunston Hall 2011 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence - L.C. Bird High School 2011 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence - L.C. Bird High School 2011 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence - Requests for Appearance 2010-2011 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence - VIP Correspondents 2010-2013 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence - White House 2013 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence - No Response 2010 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence - No Response 2010 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence - No Response 2011 2011 (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence - No Response 2011 2011 (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence - No Response 2011 2011 (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence - Official Letters 2011 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- IV. Legislative Files, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  This series consists of legislation and supporting documentation affecting the Secretary of Education, as well as state agencies assigned to the Secretariat. The bulk of these files contain the text of each bill including any amendments, bill tracking information, and Legislative Action Summaries for the various General Assembly session. For more information regarding budgetary matters related to legislative initiatives, also see Series V. Budget and Planning, 2010-2014.
  - All Students - A-F School Grades 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - All Students - A-F School Grades 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - All Students - Algebra and Early Reading 2013 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - All Students - Campaign 2012 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - All Students - Legislation 2012-2013 (1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - All Students - Legislation 2012-2013 (2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - All Students - Legislation 2012-2013 (2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - All Students - Local Charter 2013 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - All Students - Policy Development 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - All Students - Policy Development 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - All Students - Red Tape 2013 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - All Students - Science and Social Studies Waiver 2013 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - All Students - Standards of Quality Staffing 2013 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - All Students - Teach for America 2013 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - All Students - Teacher Effectiveness 2013 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - All Students - Truancy 2013 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - All Students - Venture: Jefferson-Houston Elementary School 2012 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - All Students - Venture: Memphis 2013 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - All Students - Venture: New Orleans 2012 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bill Tracking - Senate Committee 2011 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - College Lab Legislation 2010-2012 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Contracts 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Re-Authorization 2013 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General Assembly - K-12 Education Agenda 2012 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - General Assembly - House Bills: 1061-1793 2012 (Box 12, Folder 25)